<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Josh Lindsay</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Josh Lindsay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mastodon</title>
      <link>/posts/mastodon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mastodon/</guid>
      <description>Update! I really (well &amp;hellip; not much at all) tried to keep this a living document. That did not last long. It is much easier to post snippets of things as time goes on. Be sure to check out my Mastodon.technology profile!
https://mastodon.technology/@j000sh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revisit WWF Project</title>
      <link>/posts/revisit-wwf-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 13:52:39 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/revisit-wwf-project/</guid>
      <description>I have a lot of free time on my (washed) hands whilst staying inside due to COVID-19. I noticed my boyfriend got back into playing the popular Zynga game Words with Friends.
Years ago while on my commute to work, I started dabbling with mitmproxy and monitoring the network traffic and API, but never got to the meat of solving the game.
Thinking of looking back into it now, perhaps as a sequence of interview-type problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev Environment Setup</title>
      <link>/posts/shell-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2020 14:20:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/shell-setup/</guid>
      <description>Finally getting around to setting up my dotfiles and really learning how to use vim, zsh, stow, and all the tools. Going to jot down some notes for reference.
Also, I must shamefully point out that I wrote this in VS Code with the really handy markdown viewer! Maybe this could be a good first dive into editing with emacs! &amp;hellip; soon™️
Zsh Not sure I have any concrete understanding yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Personal Multi-faceted individual who enjoys learning and going places Active, personable, adventurous Software developer interested in natural language understanding Professional Software developer in the San Francisco Bay Area B.S. Computer Science from the Rochester Institute of Technology Philosophy &amp;ldquo;When was the last time you did something for the first time?&amp;rdquo;
This is a quote I cherish and live by. Every day contains a new experience, an engaging conversation, a new revelation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words With Fiends</title>
      <link>/projects/words-with-fiends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 11:57:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/words-with-fiends/</guid>
      <description>TODO extract project README here
Link: https://wwfiends.herokuapp.com/
Source: https://github.com/j000shDotCom/words-with-fire</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find My Sisig</title>
      <link>/projects/find-my-sisig/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 11:35:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/find-my-sisig/</guid>
      <description>Find that burrito! 🌯
The Senor Sisig website is quite bloated at the
Created a simple node js app that scrapes the sisig website of choice
Link: https://find-my-sisig.herokuapp.com/
Source: https://gitlab.com/jlindsay90/find-my-sisig</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/about/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/resume/</guid>
      <description>Download my resume here
Resume markdown to come!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackerRank to Git</title>
      <link>/projects/hackerrank-to-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 14:06:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hackerrank-to-git/</guid>
      <description>TODO: extract project README here
Source: https://github.com/j000shDotCom/hackerrank-to-git</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2017 13:57:43 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello world!
No idea what I am doing, but it looks like things are appearing finally. This sure has been a productive 1.5 hour flight from SFO to PHX!
I am still learning Hugo and how to create, link, and tag new posts. I think I am haphazardly getting the hang of it though. Seems simple enough. Not sure what the difference is between &amp;ldquo;+++&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;&amp;mdash;&amp;rdquo; when it comes to post/article headers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
